<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
To change this license header, choose License Headers in Project Properties.
To change this template file, choose Tools | Templates
and open the template in the editor.
-->
<ns2:itemList xmlns:ns2="items">
    <itemlist>
        <item>
            <name>dagger</name>
            <id>0</id>
            <description>
                The dagger is a knife consisting of a short blade with
                a sharply tapered point, a central spine or fuller, and two 
                cutting edges sharpened the full length of the blade.
            </description>
            <type>0</type>
            <slot>1</slot>
            <value>2</value>
            <weight>1</weight>
            <damage>4</damage>
        </item>
        <item>
            <name>shortsword</name>
            <id>1</id>
            <description>
                The shortsword is a two-edged blade made for cutting with a 
                tapered point for stabbing during thrusting. A solid grip is
                equipped with a knobbed hilt with ridges for the fingers.
            </description>
            <type>0</type>
            <slot>1</slot>
            <value>6</value>
            <weight>3</weight>
            <damage>6</damage>
        </item>
        <item>
            <name>longsword</name>
            <id>2</id>
            <description> 
                The longsword consists of a long two-edged blade measuring
                around 40 inches with a long,polished handle. The longsword 
                is very popular due to its and versatile cutting and thrusting
                abilities.
            </description>
            <type>0</type>
            <slot>1</slot>
            <value>10</value>
            <weight>4</weight>
            <damage>8</damage>
        </item>
        <item>
            <name>claymore</name>
            <id>3</id>
            <decription>
                "The claymore is a two-handed sword measuring 60-70 inches 
                overall, with an expanded cruciform hilt and a quillon block. 
            </decription>
            <type>0</type>
            <slot>3</slot>
            <value>18</value>
            <weight>8</weight>
            <damage>10</damage>
        </item>
        <item>
            <name>shortbow</name>
            <id>4</id>
            <description>
                The shortbow is a flexible shaft of wood (or horn or bone) about
                3 to 4 feet long with the ends connected by
                strong cord or a gut string that is a little shorter than the
                shaft, causing the wood to bend and keep the string under tension.
            </description>
            <type>0</type>
            <slot>3</slot>
            <value>25</value>
            <weight>2</weight>
            <damage>6</damage>
        </item>
        <item>
            <name>longbow</name>
            <id>5</id>
            <description>
                The longbow is a flexible shaft of wood (or horn or bone) about
                4 to 6 feet long with the ends connected by strong cord or a
                gut string that is a little shorter than the shaft, causing the
                wood to bend and keep the string under tension. 
            </description>
            <type>0</type>
            <slot>3</slot>
            <value>60</value>
            <weight>3</weight>
            <damage>8</damage>
        </item>
    </itemlist>

</ns2:itemList>
